JOHNNY DUNN

https://github.com/jddunn/ https://jddunn.github.io/

Summary

Full-stack dev experienced in building machine learning infrastructure and data analytics pipelines, and training and deploying models, and fine-tuning LLMs. Also experienced in web3 / smart contract development, and game development and AR / VR with Unity.

Professional Experience

Tilting Point New York, NY

Senior Blockchain Engineer

Nov 2021 – Feb 2023

- Acted as blockchain architect to build infrastructure and marketplace for full end-to-end NFT and token integrations (ERC-20
 / ERC-1155) in mobile games publisher SDK on Polygon/MATIC chain, working with MATIC engineers for best practices.
- Development of smart contracts, and help overseeing development of cryptocurrency wallet widgets and payments.

eBay New York, NY

Software Engineer 2 (Full-Stack)

June 2020 - April 2021

- Improved UX serving ads; extended REST API in Scala & Spring-Boot to service data to UI asynchronously based on active item preferences.
- Worked on scraping dashboard functionality to verify data integrity across services.
- Created deployment infrastructure process enabling rapid frontend development cycles for backend team. Set up Jenkins
 pipelines to connect underlying UI libraries, server-side rendering backends for HTML, and APIs returning ads data.

Remote

Freelance (Grapple Media, Notebrush, Edelman, HAL)

NLP Engineer / Software Engineer / Product Designer (Contract)

November 2018 - May 2021

- Created user stories, animated wireframes and functional product demo for Notebrush's MVP.
- Developed web crawling infrastructure with automated pipeline to feed data into training models for Grapple Media. Trained sentiment analysis models for text analysis for news articles.
- Trained deep learning models to create photographic filters applying artistic aesthetics of specific movies to selfies for one of Edelman's interactive Al exhibits.
- Developed / sold sentiment analysis model and infrastructure to HAL (HereAfterLegacy), and continued dev work for a year.

IPSoft New York, NY

Cognitive Implementation Engineer

June 2017 - December 2017

- Implemented modules for virtual assistant Al Amelia for corporate client-facing solutions following agile practices, working with APIs / tools provided by R&D.
- Improved workflow and productivity by writing data processing scripts to be distributed to internal teams.

Projects

Quire.work - Turn static forms and interviews into conversational experiences powered by LLMs.
 https://quire.work

Restless - Always-on anti-malware software using malicious language processing (HAN model) techniques.
 2020
 https://github.com/iddunn/restless

 Text RPG Engine - ES6 JS library to create text adventures / interactive fiction with custom player interactions. 2020 https://github.com/jddunn/text-rpg-engine

Dementia progression analysis - Dementia progression classifier for MRIs using CNN and transfer learning.
 https://github.com/jddunn/dementia-progression-analysis

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Design and Technology (May 2017) – Parsons School of Design

Awards

• 5th Place, AT&T National VR and AR Challenge, with THiNKIMMERSIVE team. (http://npe100.com/)

2017

XRC Labs Young Entrepreneurs Residential Program

Spring 2017

Skills

Programming Languages	Solidity Python Golang JavaScript Java Scala C# SQL HTML CSS SCSS
Frontend	React Next.js Redux Toolkit (RTK) Bootstrap ChakraUI MaterialUI Tailwind D3.js three.js
Backend	ethers.js HardHat LangChain FastAPI Django Keras TensorFlow PyTorch OpenCV spaCy CoreNLP NumPy SciPy pandas scikit-learn Celery Scrapy BS4 Selenium
Databases	MySQL Postgres Prisma SQLAlchemy MongoDB GraphQL Hadoop Elasticsearch Redis
DevOps	AWS (EC2, Elastic Beanstalk, Amplify, RedShift) Docker Kubernetes Jenkins
	Unity Git Postman Linux Burp Suite Adobe Creative Suite Processing openFrameworks
Tools / Software / Other	SketchUp PyCharm IntelliJ Visual Studio PyCharm PWAs Electron